topgalgames.com 2015-05-15

# Top Gal Games - Privacy Policy

**Safety:**

Your safety and privacy is our at most importance and hence, we don’t collect any personal details from our visitors. Topgalgames.com is a place for games for people above 13 years of age and persons aging below this are advised to seek the assistance of their respective parents. 

**Use of Cookies and Log files:**

We make use of cookies and log files to understand our visitors better in terms of their places and visiting patterns to know their preferences that we can serve our visitors with most suitable contents.

 **Third Party Advertisements:**

You can come across third party advertisements served by Google AdSense or any other ad serving agencies for that matter. While we don’t share with them any of your non personal information, they may use cookies and web beacons in order to sever you with relevant and most suitable ads. When you share your personal information with the third party advertising agencies, you are only responsible for whatever information you give and we cannot be held responsible in any manner. 

We have also links leading to our partners’ sites which are in similar nature with our site. But they have their own privacy policy. Hence, it is entirely your responsibility to read their privacy policy before using their sites as we cannot have any control or responsibility for their privacy policy. 

Once you start using our site, it is understood that you are agreeing to our privacy policy. Topgalgames.com has the exclusive right to change its privacy policy whenever it feels it necessary and it may do it without giving you prior intimation. Therefore, you are requested to read the privacy policy every now then.
